Guide to the Rose Goldsen papers, [ca. 1950-1985]
Goldsen, Rose papers, [ca. 1950-1985]
- Series III.Correspondence
  - Alphabetical
    - National Endowment for the Humanities 12/78-11/79 (Box 8, Folder 56)
      [RKG evaluations of grant proposals]
    - 0-P (Box 8, Folder 57)
      [Kevin O'Neill 2/83; David L. Paletz 5/80; Francim Patterson (The Gorilla Foundation) 3/79; Carl Perrian 2/72; Michael Pollak 2-12/80; Anneliese A. Pontius 2-3/77, "Frontal Lobe System Maturation Lag.." 1976, "The Face in Sacred Art of the Upper Sepik River.." 10/74]
    - Malcolm and Marcia Odell 1/80 (Box 8, Folder 58)
      [c.v.'s; Odell and Odell, "The Evolution of a Strategy for Communal Area Livestoc Development in Botswana" 9/79]
    - Sandra Ospina c. 1973-3/81 (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - Reynaldo Pareja 2/72-4/81 (Box 8, Folder 60)
      [student records; draft chapters of thesis; "Perfil de la Percepcion Visual de: Campesino Hondureno" 1979]
    - Arthur Paris 6/77-6/80 (Box 8, Folder 61)
      ["'Blacks Britannica":. Race, Cinema, and the Public Sphere" 12/79]
    - R (Box 8, Folder 62)
      [Mary Richards (Cerrache TV) 4/79 - w/ article on Nickelodeon cable network; Miles Roberts 8/80; Michael J. Robinson 6-7/80; Thomas Rogers 5/79; Norman P. Ross 8-9/79]
    - German w. Rama c. 1974-81 (Box 8, Folder 63)
    - O. Lee Reed 2-10/80 (Box 8, Folder 64)
    - S (Box 8, Folder 65)
      [Satellite News. 9/919/79; Wavne Satz - notes 9-10/8 Steven H. Scheuer (All About TV, Inc.) - re circulation of RKG columns 5-6/80; Barry Siegel (L.A. Times) 5/79-1/80; Frank Stanton 8/80; Richard Startup, c.v., "Statement of Research and Teaching Interests.."; Christopher D. Stone 7-8/79]
    - Gabriela and Marisa Samper 3-8/79 (Box 8, Folder 66)
      [booklet & newspaper article about G. Samper; William Rogers correspondence w/ M. Samper and her attorney]
    - Alfredo Sanchez 1/73-12/74 (Box 8, Folder 67)
      [English and Spanish; "Communications Economics Final Paper" 1972; "Gregory Bateson's Theory of Communications: A First Approach" 1973; "The Reading Experience as a Cultural Phenomenon 1973]
    - Herbert I. Schiller 7/71-11/76 (Box 8, Folder 68)
    - Herbert Schiller - ICODES Seminar 3/75 ["The Appearance of National-Communications Policies.." 2/75 (Box 8, Folder 69)
    - Michael Shamberg - visiting lecture 11/28/73 T correspondence, publicity. Cornell Sun article! (Box 8, Folder 70)
    - T-V (Box 8, Folder 71)
      [TV Guide (Cathy Johnson) 10-11/78; Luis E. Varela 2-4/81; Michael D. Veley 7/80; Vermont Castings 9/79; Villaae Desian 2/81]
    - Nicholas Tavuchis 8/75-5/82 (Box 8, Folder 72)
      [c.v.'s; James C. Chambers and Tavuchis, "Kids and kin: children's understanding of American kin terms" 12/74]
    - Nicholas Tavuchis - Recommendations 11/72-4/79 (Box 8, Folder 73)
    - Ross Tharaud 2/75-7/80 (Box 8, Folder 74)
      [essays, poems]
    - W (Box 9, Folder 1)
      [Ray E. Wakeley 2-7/81; Barbel Wallisch-Prinz 9/79-1/80; William F. Whyte 6/79, 11/80; Eyerett K. Wilson (. 8/79, "Sociology: Scholarly Discipline or Profession?" 9/77; Langdon Winner 3-4/80; Congressman Timothy E. Wirth 9/78]
    - Catalina Wainerman 12/78-1/84 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      [English and Spanish; Cesar Vapnarsky, "Toward Scientific Foundations for the Determination of Localities in Population Censuses" 1978]
    - Evan L. Webster 7/77-11/82 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Lenore J. Weitzman 3/75-12/80 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      [c.v.'s]
    - Lenore Weitzman - recommendations, Cornell visit 9/82-4/83 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      [c.v. 's, statements of plans]
    - Joseph Weizenbaum 11/78-6/79 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      [RKG notes on Weizenbaum, Computer Power and Human Reason; Georqe Alexander, "Terminal Therapy" 9/78]
    - Kent Wood (Utah State) conference call 6/18/82 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - T.R. Young 5-11/82 (Box 9, Folder 8)
      [c.v; Fran -- to RKG, n.d.; visiting lecture 11/82 - correspondence, publicity, notes]
    - Monserrat Zayas 6/79-1/83 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Phillip C. Zimbardo 6-10/73 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Chronological Files (in reverse chronological order)
    - 1980-84 Correspondence to be filed [English and Spanish (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - 1979-80 Chronological file (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - 1978 Chronological file (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - 1977 Chronological file (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - 1977 Chronological file (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - 1976 Chronological file (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - 1972 Correspondence - unclassified (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Recommendations - Cornell Sociology Department faculty (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - 1983 Recommendations (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - 1981-2 Recommendations (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - 1977-80 Recommendations (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - 1974-76 Recommendations (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Series IV. Teaching
  - Course Materials
    - Sociology 100.1 Fall 1979
      - Soc 100.1, Fall 1979 - Syllabus, assignments, notes (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - Soc 100.1, Fall 1979 - Students' schedules, class lists (Box 10, Folder 2)
      - Soc 100.1, Fall 1979 - Student notes on Castaneda debat (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - Soc 100.1, Fall 1979 - Final papers (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Soc. 100.1, Fall 1979 - Student Papers
      - Bradt, Rick (Box 10, Folder 5)
      - Gordon, Jim (Box 10, Folder 6)
      - Haun, Chris (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - Hentschel, Susan (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - Hoskins, Bruce (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - Lesser, Karen (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Lewin, Howard (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - Loehr, Dan (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - Mori, Terry (Box 10, Folder 13)
      - Pang, Niu Kian (Box 10, Folder 14)
      - Pfeiffer, Eileen (Box 10, Folder 15)
      - Sun, Donald (Box 10, Folder 16)
      - Thompson, Bryan (Box 10, Folder 17)
      - Sheon, Amy (Box 10, Folder 18)
      - Trell, Lisa (Box 10, Folder 19)
      - Walsh, Kevin (Box 10, Folder 20)
      - Wexler, Elaine 45 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Soc. 100.1 Fall 1984
      - Soc 100.1, Fall 1984 - Class list, book orders, RKG notes (Box 10, Folder 22)
      - Soc 100.1, Fall 1984 - Freshman seminar information (Box 10, Folder 23)
      - Soc 100.1, Fall 1984 - "Time" and "Baseball" exercises with RKG notes (Box 10, Folder 24)
      - Soc 100.1, Fall 1984 - Student essay examples (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Sociology 100.2 1977-78
      - Soc 100.2, Fall 1978 - Students enrolled, procedures, course handouts (Box 10, Folder 26)
      - Soc 100.2, 1977, 1978 - General instructions, assignments, bibliography (Box 10, Folder 27)
      - Soc 100.2, Fall 1978 - Book review examples - on Mencken, Welles, Gogol, Wolfe, etc. (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Soc. 100.2, Fall 1978 - Student Papers
      - Alterman, Randi (Box 10, Folder 29)
      - Behrooz, Maryam (Box 10, Folder 30)
      - Chin, David (Box 10, Folder 31)
      - Conner s, Leisha (Box 10, Folder 32)
      - De Luca, Craig (Box 10, Folder 33)
      - Ferrell, Brad (Box 10, Folder 34)
      - Ho, Michael D. (Box 10, Folder 35)
      - Goldsborough, Stacy (Box 10, Folder 36)
      - Goldman, Barbara (Box 10, Folder 37)
      - Hulsair, Margaret (Box 10, Folder 38)
      - Jeffrey, Barbara (Box 10, Folder 39)
      - Kasper, Robert 46 (Box 10, Folder 40)
      - Lockwood, Jay (Box 10, Folder 41)
      - Sachs, Heather (Box 10, Folder 42)
      - Pinnisi, Michael (Box 10, Folder 43)
      - Seiden, Mark (Box 10, Folder 44)
      - Shope, William J. (Box 10, Folder 45)
      - Szymkowiak, Ed (Box 10, Folder 46)
      - Wallach, Wendy (Box 10, Folder 47)
      - Warner, Marie (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - Freshman Seminar Article Files (eg for Soc 100.2 Fall 1978)
      - Lecture: David Gerrold. The World of Star Trek (Box 10, Folder 49)
      - Lecture: Orwell and 1984 (Box 10, Folder 50)
      - Goldsen, Rose K. - Examples of diary (Box 10, Folder 51)
      - Graffiti (Box 10, Folder 52)
      - Images, signs, hieroglyphics (Box 10, Folder 53)
      - Jargon: "The Crisis Explained," "Vogue Words," "Jargon (Box 10, Folder 54)
      - Article files, part I (Box 10, Folder 55)
      - Article files, part II (Box 10, Folder 56)
      - John Leonard (Box 10, Folder 57)
      - Jerome Lettvin, "On Seeing Sidelong" (Box 10, Folder 58)
      - George Orwell (Box 10, Folder 59)
      - William Safire - selected columns (Box 10, Folder 60)
    - Sociology 101 1982-84
      - Soc 101, Fall 1982 - Syllabus, notes, readings (Box 10, Folder 61)
      - Soc 101, Fall 1982 - continued 47 (Box 10, Folder 62)
      - Soc 101, Spring 1983 (Box 10, Folder 63)
      - Soc 101, Fall 1984 - Cornell in Washington - notes, readings (Box 10, Folder 64)
    - Soc. 103/Hist Art 105, Fall 1980 "Myth, Image And Modern Society" (RKG/Peter Kahn)
      - Soc 103, Fall 1980 - Readings, assignments (Box 10, Folder 65)
      - Soc 103, Fall 1980 - Bibliography - symbols, cognitive processes (Box 10, Folder 66)
      - Soc 103, Fall 1980 - Course notes (Box 10, Folder 67)
      - Soc 103, Fall 1980 - RKG notes (Box 10, Folder 68)
      - Soc 103, Fall 1980 - Comments on student essays (Box 10, Folder 69)
      - Soc 103, Fall 1980 - Articles (Box 10, Folder 70)
      - Soc 103, Fall 1980 - Articles, notes - mythologies, astronauts (Box 10, Folder 71)
      - Soc 103, Fall 1980 - Earl W. Count, "Myth as World View (Box 10, Folder 72)
      - Soc 103, Fall 1980 - Symbol (Box 10, Folder 73)
      - Language and myth (Box 10, Folder 74)
      - Numbers - myth and social learning (Box 10, Folder 75)
      - Sabbath ritual (Yom Kippur - driving) (Box 10, Folder 76)
        [RKG notes 5pp]
      - Meaning resides in context - Llurhos, Nacirema (Box 10, Folder 77)
      - Context and context markers (Box 10, Folder 78)
        [RKG notes 8pp]
    - Soc. 105 "Mass Media And Society," Fall 1983
      - Soc 105, Fall 1983? - class lists, notes, readings (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - Soc 105, Fall 1983? - readings (folder 1) (Box 11, Folder 2)
      - Soc 105, Fall 1983? - readings (folder 2) (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - Soc 105? Fall 1983? - Carry - Joint committee on TV an children (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - Soc 105, Fall 1983 - Freshman seminar guidelines, writing workshop information (Box 11, Folder 5)
      - Soc 105, Fall 1983 - List of assignments, students registered (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - Soc 105, Fall 1983 - Class notes (Box 11, Folder 7)
      - Soc 105, Fall 1983 - Cut and paste exercises: "Time," "Baseball," "TV Commercials," and "Marlboro" (Box 11, Folder 8)
      - Soc 105, Fall 1983 - "Time" and "Baseball" assignments returned (Box 11, Folder 9)
      - Soc 105, Fall 1983 - Articles (Box 11, Folder 10)
      - Soc 105, Fall 1983 - RKG notes - Barthes (Box 11, Folder 11)
      - Soc 105, Fall 1983 - Evaluations by students (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Sociology 152 1976-77
      - Soc 152, Fall 1976 - Can opener exercise and article (New York Times) (Box 11, Folder 13)
      - Soc 152, Fall 1977 - Individual notes, leftover editinc job unsigned (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Soc. 152, Fall 1977 - Student Papers [group A]
      - Albahaney, Scott (Box 11, Folder 15)
      - Boggs, Rick (Box 11, Folder 16)
      - Chartier, Christopher (Box 11, Folder 17)
      - Cohn, Nina (Box 11, Folder 18)
      - Simon, Joanne (Box 11, Folder 19)
      - Cogger, Steve (Box 11, Folder 20)
      - Costello, Tim (Box 11, Folder 21)
      - Floersheimer, Rhea (Box 11, Folder 22)
      - Fleites, Lourdes (Box 11, Folder 23)
      - Gordon, David (Box 11, Folder 24)
      - Gordon, Ruth (Box 11, Folder 25)
      - Haas, Nancy (Box 11, Folder 26)
      - Herman, Alice (Box 11, Folder 27)
      - Kasanoff, Larry (Box 11, Folder 28)
      - Lamothe, Mark (Box 11, Folder 29)
      - Litman, Jo Lynn (Box 11, Folder 30)
      - Purcell, Eric (Box 11, Folder 31)
      - Schmuckler, Eric (Box 11, Folder 32)
      - Schwartz, Marc (Box 11, Folder 33)
      - Wood, Dan (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Soc. 152, Fall 1977 - Student Papers [group B]
      - Berland, Laurie (Box 11, Folder 35)
      - Bialer, Cindy (Box 11, Folder 36)
      - Danzker, Richard (Box 11, Folder 37)
      - Freidmutter, Jill (Box 11, Folder 38)
      - Hill, R. Bradley (Box 11, Folder 39)
      - Landauer, Robert (Box 11, Folder 40)
      - Leavitt, John (Box 11, Folder 41)
      - Lobosco, John 50 (Box 11, Folder 42)
      - Martin, Mike (Box 11, Folder 43)
      - Nelson, Karen (Box 11, Folder 44)
      - Reed, Robert (Box 11, Folder 45)
      - Seiler, Gary (Box 11, Folder 46)
      - Shulte, Lynne (Box 11, Folder 47)
      - Steinfeld, Eduardo (Box 11, Folder 48)
      - Thompson, Scott (Box 11, Folder 49)
      - Soc 152, Fall 1979 - Teaching devices (debate/role playing) (Box 11, Folder 50)
      - Soc 201, Fall 1983? - Bibliographic notes (Box 11, Folder 51)
      - Soc 201, n.d. - Earlier modules (Box 11, Folder 52)
    - Soc. 205/Ling 205 "Understanding The Language OF Television Images," Fall 1982 (RKG/Linda Waugh)
      - Soc 205/Ling 205, Fall 1982 - RKG notebook (Box 11, Folder 53)
      - Soc 205/Ling 205, Fall 1982 - RKG Log I - 9/6-10/20/82 (Box 11, Folder 54)
      - Soc 205/Ling 205, Fall 1982 - RKG Log II - 10/20/82- (Box 11, Folder 55)
      - Soc 205/Ling 205, Fall 1982 - Syllabus, readings, cours description, correspondence (Box 11, Folder 56)
      - Soc 205/Ling 205, Fall 1982 - Class lists (Box 11, Folder 57)
      - [Soc 205/Ling 205, Fall 1982?] - Intellectual journal examples - RKG, Chris Raymond (Box 11, Folder 58)
      - Soc 205/Ling 205, Fall 1982 - articles (Box 11, Folder 59)
      - Soc 205/Ling 205, Fall 1982 - articles - Jonathan Price (Box 11, Folder 60)
    - Soc. 205/Ling 205, Fall 1982 - Student Papers
      - Bluestein, Lisa (final paper, intellectual journal) (Box 11, Folder 61)
      - LaForge, Pat 51 (Box 11, Folder 62)
      - Martin, Licia (Box 11, Folder 63)
      - Miller, Kathryn (Box 11, Folder 64)
      - Simon, Laura (Box 11, Folder 65)
      - Wilansky, Steve (Box 11, Folder 66)
      - Kleinberg, Zax, Isaacson, Babka (Box 11, Folder 67)
    - Sociology 252 1977-79
      - Soc 252, Spring 1977 - Sample student essays prepared for exams (Box 11, Folder 68)
      - Soc 252, Spring 1977 - Bibliography (Box 11, Folder 69)
      - Soc 252, Spring 1977 - Nuts and bolts: TA minutes, TA evaluation (Box 11, Folder 70)
      - Soc 252, Spring 1978 "Public Opinion" - Course outline and reading list (Box 11, Folder 71)
      - Soc 252, Spring 1978 - Lecture One 1/31/78 - WatzlawicK (use with Berger) (Box 11, Folder 72)
      - Soc 252, Spring 1978 - Prelim I, Prelim II, Final Prelim (Box 11, Folder 73)
      - Soc 252, Spring 1979 "Public Opinion" - Syllabus, assignments, book lists (Box 11, Folder 74)
      - Soc 252, Spring 1979 - Lectures (Box 11, Folder 75)
      - Soc 252, Spring 1979 - Prelims (Box 11, Folder 76)
    - Soc. 252, Spring 1979 "Public Opinion" - Final Exams
      - Accardo, Michael (Box 11, Folder 77)
      - Bo ley, Lynn Kay (Box 11, Folder 78)
      - Brooks, Priscilla (Box 11, Folder 79)
      - Chatani, Kiki (Box 11, Folder 80)
      - Chunglo, Stephen (Box 11, Folder 81)
      - Cobert, Robert (Box 11, Folder 82)
      - Creedon, Laurie (Box 11, Folder 83)
      - Damon, Gregg (Box 11, Folder 84)
      - Davison, Mark (Box 11, Folder 85)
      - Dunbar, Bill (Box 11, Folder 86)
      - Dunn, Scott (Box 11, Folder 87)
      - Gavris, Lee (Box 11, Folder 88)
      - Gordon, Howard (Box 11, Folder 89)
      - Hardie, Ann (Box 11, Folder 90)
      - Heller, Susan (Box 11, Folder 91)
      - Klein, Cheryl (Box 11, Folder 92)
      - Lazar, Jerry (Box 11, Folder 93)
      - McGill, Patricia (Box 11, Folder 94)
      - Nagengast, Ivy Lee (Box 11, Folder 95)
      - Nilsson, Lisa (Box 11, Folder 96)
      - O'Meara, Vicki (Box 11, Folder 97)
      - Prouty, Eve (Box 11, Folder 98)
      - Ray nor, Ellen (Box 11, Folder 99)
      - Schwarz, Adrienne (Box 11, Folder 100)
      - Schwartz, June (Box 11, Folder 101)
      - Seidenberg, Michael (Box 11, Folder 102)
      - Selling, Bernie (Box 11, Folder 103)
      - Slatkin, Thomas (Box 11, Folder 104)
      - Stein, William (Box 11, Folder 105)
      - West, Stacy (Box 11, Folder 106)
      - Zimetbaum, Jane (Box 11, Folder 107)
    - Soc. 252 "Public Opinion, " 1980-83
      - Soc 252, Spring 1980 "Public Opinion" - Syllabus, readings, prelim questions (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - Soc 252, Spring 1980 - Mark Maier (TA) section reading guides; Andrea Vebell (student) reading notes (Box 12, Folder 2)
      - Soc 252, Spring 1980 - Outstanding student projects (part l) (Box 12, Folder 3)
      - Soc 252, Spring 1980 - Outstanding student projects (part 2) (Box 12, Folder 4)
      - Soc 252, Spring 1981 - Course outline, readings, assignments, notes, correspondence (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - Soc 252, Spring 1981 - Prelims (Box 12, Folder 6)
      - Soc 252, Summer 1981 - Exam, Mark Maier TA journal (Box 12, Folder 7)
      - Soc 252, Fall 1981 - RKG lectures 11/4, 11/6 (Box 12, Folder 8)
      - Soc 252, Summer 1982 - Jon McAdams - Syllabus, paper topics, quizzes (Box 12, Folder 9)
      - Soc 252, Spring 1983 "Public Opinion" - Syllabus, bibliography (Box 12, Folder 10)
      - Soc 252, Spring 1983 - Lecture notes, course materials (Box 12, Folder 11)
      - [Soc 252, Spring 1983?] - 3/8/83 - course notes? (Box 12, Folder 12)
      - Soc 252, Spring 1983 - Final exam, paper proposal, exa questions (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Soc. 252, Spring 1983 "Public Opinion" - Student Papers
      - Atwood, Kathryn (Box 12, Folder 14)
      - Beyer, Jeffrey (Box 12, Folder 15)
      - Budin, Beth Michele (Box 12, Folder 16)
      - Castillo, Cristina (Box 12, Folder 17)
      - Crum, Nancy (Box 12, Folder 18)
      - Davis, Sherrell (Box 12, Folder 19)
      - Egeth, Bennett (Box 12, Folder 20)
      - Elias, Maria (Box 12, Folder 21)
      - Hopkins, Samuel R. (Box 12, Folder 22)
      - Hudanich, Sarah (Box 12, Folder 23)
      - Jacobs, Julie (Box 12, Folder 24)
      - Krasnopolsky, Linda (Box 12, Folder 25)
      - Kupfer, Lori (Box 12, Folder 26)
      - Levine, Julie (Box 12, Folder 27)
      - Netter, Patricia J. (Box 12, Folder 28)
      - Peterson, Kathryn (Box 12, Folder 29)
      - Pietrucha, Frank (Box 12, Folder 30)
      - Reitano, Kirn (Box 12, Folder 31)
      - Richard, Ann (Box 12, Folder 32)
      - Roberts, Amy (Box 12, Folder 33)
      - Schmidt, Karen Lee - short papers (Box 12, Folder 34)
      - Schmidt, Karen Lee - final paper (Box 12, Folder 35)
      - Schuler, Richard (Box 12, Folder 36)
      - Sutton, Stewart (Box 12, Folder 37)
      - Westa, Anne (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Soc. 252, Summer-Fall 1983
      - Soc 252, Summer 1983 - Jon McAdams syllabus (Box 12, Folder 39)
      - Soc 252, Fall 1983 - Enrollment, readings, miscellaneous (Box 12, Folder 40)
      - Soc 252, Fall 1983 - Readings for Module 2 (9/14-10/4)- spiral-bound booklet (Box 12, Folder 41)
      - Soc 252, Fall 1983 - Course notes (Box 12, Folder 42)
      - Soc 252, Fall 1983 - Course notes, continued (Box 12, Folder 43)
      - Soc 252, [Fall 1983?] - RKG notes - steno notebook (Box 12, Folder 44)
      - [Soc 105 and 252?], [Fall 1983?] - RKG notes - steno notebook (Box 12, Folder 45)
      - Soc 252, Fall 1983 - Student papers on "The Day After" (Box 12, Folder 46)
      - Soc 252, Fall 1983 - Student presentations (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - Soc. 252, Fall 1984
      - Soc 252, Fall 1984 - Readings, syllabus, paper assignments, class lists (Box 12, Folder 48)
      - Soc 252, [Fall 1984?] - Readings, notes (Box 12, Folder 49)
      - Soc 252, Fall 1984 - Class notes (Box 12, Folder 50)
      - RKG steno book - unlabeled (Fall 1984) (Box 12, Folder 51)
      - RKG steno book - labeled (?) "Habermas" (Box 12, Folder 52)
      - Soc 252, Fall 1984 - Prelim questions 1 & 2, samples o] Question 1 (Box 12, Folder 53)
      - Soc 252, Fall 1984 - Final prelim, with grading guidelines (Box 12, Folder 54)
      - Soc 252, Fall 1984 - Final prelim, grading sheets for students (Box 12, Folder 55)
      - Soc 252, Fall 1984 - Kihoon Urn final paper 12/14/84 (Box 12, Folder 56)
      - Soc 252, Fall 1984 - Old exams (Box 12, Folder 57)
      - [Soc 252?] - RKG notes - Barnow (Box 12, Folder 58)
      - [RKG course log for Soc 252, 100, 591] - Fall (Box 12, Folder 59)
        [1984?]
    - Soc. 262, 1973-76
      - Soc 262, Spring 1973 - Syllabus, readings, paper topics (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - Soc 262, Spring 1973 - Final prelim (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - Soc 262, Fall 1973 - Readings, exams, paper topics (Box 13, Folder 3)
      - Soc 262, Fall 1974 - Bibliography and syllabus (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - Soc 262, Fall 1974 - Prelims (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Soc 262, Fall 1974 - Washington - assistants (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - Soc 262, Spring 1976 - Bibliography, Campus Store order forms (Box 13, Folder 7)
      - Soc 262, Spring 1976 - RKG notes (Box 13, Folder 8)
      - Soc 262, Spring 1976 - Prelim 3/18-23/76; Final prelim 5/4-11/76 (Box 13, Folder 9)
      - Soc 262, Spring 1976 - Sample exam questions - student papers (Box 13, Folder 10)
      - Soc 262, Fall 1976 - Michael Levine prelim, notes, correspondence (Box 13, Folder 11)
      - Soc 252/262 - Article files, reserve readings (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Soc. 350, 462 and 691
      - Soc 350, Spring 1984 "Communications and Social Policy1 (Cornell-in-Washington) (Box 13, Folder 13)
      - Soc 462, Fall 1973 - Syllabus, assignment, summary (Box 13, Folder 14)
      - Soc 462, [Fall 1976 or later] - Bibliography (Box 13, Folder 15)
      - Soc 462, Spring 1978 "Theoretical Approaches to the Sociology of Communications" (Box 13, Folder 16)
      - Soc 462/691, Spring 1978 - Students (Box 13, Folder 17)
      - Soc 462, Fall 1978 - C. Wright Mills bibliography (11/78) (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Soc. 462, Spring 1980 - Student Projects
      - Lewis Clark, John McAdams, Ronnie Schwartz (Box 13, Folder 19)
      - Sue Kurz (Box 13, Folder 20)
      - Tomas Lopez-Pumarejo (Box 13, Folder 21)
      - Rafael Ramos (Box 13, Folder 22)
      - Steve Ross (Box 13, Folder 23)
      - Terri Toles (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Soc. 462, Spring 1983
      - Soc 462, Spring 1983 "Society and Consciousness" - Class lists (Box 13, Folder 25)
      - Soc 462, Spring 1983 - Assignments (Box 13, Folder 26)
      - Soc 462, Spring 1983 - Assignments, miscellaneous - deaf child script, video script (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Soc. 462, Spring 1983 - Final Projects
      - Jack Ascher (Box 13, Folder 28)
      - Lee Bender (Box 13, Folder 29)
      - Stephen Hilgartner (Box 13, Folder 30)
      - John Lerner (Box 13, Folder 31)
      - Beth Littman (Box 13, Folder 32)
      - Patricia Netter (Box 13, Folder 33)
      - Kathy Orr (Box 13, Folder 34)
      - Matthew Sirota (Box 13, Folder 35)
      - Steven Tyndall (Box 13, Folder 36)
      - Soc 491, Spring 1981 - Seminar (Box 13, Folder 37)
      - Soc 641, Spring 1974 [?] - Methods seminar -Bibliography and summary (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - "America And World Community," 1978-84
      - "America and World Community," 3/8, 3/13, 3/15/78 (Box 13, Folder 39)
      - "America and World Community," 2/23, 2/25, 3/2/81 (Box 13, Folder 40)
      - "America and World Community," Spring 1983; Center for World Community project; Bob Beggs letters 9-10/82 (Box 13, Folder 41)
      - "America and World Community"?, Spring 1983? (Box 13, Folder 42)
      - "America and World Community," Spring 1984? (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - Informal/ Independent Studies - Fall 1978 - Spring 1980
      - Informal Study, Spring 1979: Donna Cohn, Eric Schmuckler, Larry Kasanoff, Steve Seidman - student papers (Box 13, Folder 44)
      - Donna Cohn, Fall 1978 - Spring 1979 (Box 13, Folder 45)
      - Ira Diamant, Fall 1978 (Box 13, Folder 46)
      - Larry Kasanoff, Spring 1979, Spring 1980 (Box 13, Folder 47)
      - Eric Schmuckler, Fall 1978 - Spring 1979 (Box 13, Folder 48)
      - Consumer Product Safety Commission - rules for toys (Box 13, Folder 49)